Guide to the Public Art Fund Archive 1966-2009 MSS.270
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIII: Data Storage, 179241
  - Artspace San Antonio / ArtTalks: Rochelle Steiner/ Towards a Livable City -- 30 Years of Public Art Fund Projects in New York, 2008; 201982 (Box 110, Media ID: 270.3.0111)
  - Rochelle's Presentation / San Francisco November 2008 / Powerpoint, 201983 (Box 110, Media ID: 270.3.0112)
  - Rochelle San Francisco CCA - November 2008 / Seminar 1 - Seminar 2, 201984 (Box 110, Media ID: 270.3.0113)
  - Rochelle Lecture CCA San Francisco November 2008, 201985 (Box 110, Media ID: 270.3.0114)
  - Rochelle Atlanta December 2008 Powerpoint presentation, 201986 (Box 110, Media ID: 270.3.0115)
  - back-up CD #2 Rochelle Steiner Powerpoint, undated; 201987 (Box 110, Media ID: 270.3.0116)
- Series XIV: Objects, 197026
  This series contains a number of objects from the Public Art Fund Archive. Items in this series include an original headset and walk-man used at the site of Janet Cardiff's "Her Long Black Hair" (2005), and an original work of art from Ilya Kabokov's "Monument to the Glove."
  - Projection Lenses for 35mm slides / Focal Length 1" (25.4mm) - f/2.8, undated; 200753 (Box 111, Object ID: 270.2.0001)
  - Projection Lenses for 35mm slides / Focal Length 1" (25.4mm) - f/2.8, undated; 200754 (Box 111, Object ID: 270.2.0002)
  - Projection Lenses for 35mm slides / Focal Length 1" (25.4mm) - f/2.8 - S/N 27492, undated; 200755 (Box 111, Object ID: 270.2.0003)
  - Projection Lenses for 35mm slides / Focal Length 1" (25.4mm) - f/2.8 - S/N 27545, undated; 200756 (Box 111, Object ID: 270.2.0004)
  - Certificate of Recognition presented by David Dinkins, 1993; 200761 (Box 111)
  - Lawrence Weiner - 6 Pins, undated; 200762 (Box 111)
  - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - original headset with discman and booklet, 2005; 200763 (Box 111)
  - Kabakov's glove - "Monument to the Lost Glove", 1997; cuid5974; 199488; 1 item one sculpture (Box 112)
    Scope and Contents
    Artist: Ilya Kabakov
    Sculpture (visual works)
- Series XV: Printed Material, 1963-2008; 7 Linear Feet in 7 record cartons.
  This series contains printed material donated with the collection.
  - The Ablah Collection. Museum Without Walls: Henry Moore: In New York City, undated (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Alex Rosenberg Gallery. Henry Moore: Sculpture, Drawings, Prints, 1981 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Alternative Museum. Houston Conwill: The Passion of St. Matthew, 1986 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Amelie A. Wallace Gallery. Landscape/Sculpture, 1981 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Al Held: New Paintings, 1992 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Anne Truitt: Sculpture 1961-1991 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Anthony Caro: An Exhibition of Recent Sculpture…, 1994 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Anthony Caro: The Greek Series, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Anthony Caro: New Sculpture, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Arthur Gibbons: New Sculpture, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Beverly Pepper, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Beverly Pepper: New Sculpture, 1984 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Beverly Pepper: New Work 1981-1982 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Beverly Pepper: Private-Scale Sculpture 1966-1987 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Beverly Pepper: The Umbrian Bronze Markers, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Karel Appel: Recent Work, 1992 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery. Sculpture Out of Doors, undated (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - Arctander, A. Eric. Artemisia: Selected Letters/Tunnel Series: Drawings, undated (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - AREA, Inc. Area Sculpture - Ward's Island, undated (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - AREA, Inc. Area Sculpture - Ward's Island May 1980 - April 1981 (Box 133, Folder 20)
  - AREA, Inc. "Sculpture on Shoreline Sites", 1979 (Box 133, Folder 21)
  - Arlington Arts Center, and Maryland Art Place. Home, 1992 (Box 133, Folder 22)
  - Art Center of South Bend. George Rickey in South Bend, 1985 (Box 133, Folder 23)
  - Art Commission of the City of New York. National Directory of Design Review Agencies, 1991 (Box 133, Folder 24)
  - Art Gallery of Ontario in Toronto. Henry Moore Remembered, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 25)
  - Art Industrie. Forrest Myers, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 26)
  - Art Industrie. Forrest Myers, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 27)
  - Art in General. Josely Carvalho, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 28)
  - Artpark. Momentary Halt, 1982 (Box 133, Folder 29)
  - Artpark. Artpark 1977: The Program in Visual Arts (Box 133, Folder 30)
  - Artpark. Artpark 1978: The Program in Visual Arts (Box 133, Folder 31)
  - Artpark. Artpark 1979 (Box 133, Folder 32)
  - Artpark. Artpark 1980: Visual Arts (Box 133, Folder 33)
  - Artpark. Artpark '81/Lewiston, New York: Visual Arts, 1981 (Box 133, Folder 34)
  - Artpark. Artpark 1982/Visual Arts (Box 133, Folder 35)
  - Artpark. Artpark: Visual Arts 1983 (Box 133, Folder 36)
  - Arts Council of New South Wales. The Mural Manual, 1982 (Box 133, Folder 37)
  - Arts Councils of America. The Arts: A Central Element of a Good Society, 1965 (Box 133, Folder 38)
  - Arts Councils of America. The Politics of Art, 1966 (Box 133, Folder 39)
  - Arts in Society. The Politics of Art, 1974 (Box 133, Folder 40)
  - Arts in Society vol. 12 no. 1: The Surge of Community Arts, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 41)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts. The Arts: Planning for Change, 1966 (Box 133, Folder 42)
  - Baumann, Walter. Cow Parade, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 43)
  - Bernar Venet: Sculptures, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 44)
  - Bette Stoler Gallery. Ursula von Rydingsvard, 1984 (Box 133, Folder 45)
  - Blekinge Museum. Three Public Projects, undated (Box 133, Folder 46)
  - BlumHelman Gallery. Ellsworth Kelly, 1986 (Box 133, Folder 47)
  - BlumHelman Gallery. Robert Lobe: New Work, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 48)
  - Bourdon, David. Carl Andre: Sculptrue 1959-1977, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 49)
  - Burchfield Art Center. Ghost City, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 50)
  - California State University, Fullerton - Main Art Gallery. The Photographic: Two Points of View, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 51)
  - Cambridge Arts Council. Arts on the Line, 1980 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Art Foundation, and the Museum of Fine Arts, Museum of New Mexico. Linda Fleming: Tangible Mind, 1998 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Capotondi dal 1964 al 1977 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Caro, Anthony. The York Sculptures, undated (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Castle Clinton. Interpretations '79, undated (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Centre d'Art Contemporain Pablo Neruda Corbeil-Essones, and Leopold-Hoesch-Museum Duren R.F.A.. Michel Gerard, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Centre National d'Art Contemporain de Grenoble. Pat Steir: La Ligne du Coeur: The Heart Line, 1992 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - City of New York Parks & Recreation. Eight Seasons, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - City of New York Parks & Recreation. Noah's Art, 1989 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art. Artists + Architects, 1985 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art. David Saunders, 1984 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Comune di Milano. Staccioli, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Contemporary Sculpture Center, Tokyo. Henry Moore, 1981 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - Cooper-Hewitt Museum. Outdoor Art in New York, undated (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - The Cooper Union School of Art. Ghostcatching, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - The Culture Stations Project, 1983 (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Dallas Parks and Recreation Department. Visual Dallas: A Public Art Plan for the City, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - DC Moore Gallery. Robert Kushner, 1998 (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - Delaware Art Museum. Donna Dennis: Deep Stations, 1988 (Box 134, Folder 19)
  - District of Columbia Redevelopment Land Agency. Final Report: Doiwntown Washington Streets for People, 1973 (Box 134, Folder 20)
  - Di Suvero, Mark. Chalon/s/saone: une population, un sculpteur 1972/4, undated (Box 134, Folder 21)
  - Documenta 8: Kassel, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 22)
  - Domini Public, 1994 (Box 134, Folder 23)
  - Eastern State Penitentiary. Prison Sentences, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 24)
  - Eighty, undated (Box 134, Folder 25)
  - Elizabeth Harris Gallery. John Monti, 1998 (Box 134, Folder 26)
  - Encounters on the Road of Borders, undated (Box 134, Folder 27)
  - The Equitable Gallery. Views from a Golden Hill, 1996 (Box 134, Folder 28)
  - Ernkist, Paivi. Konsten I Hogskolan Gavle-Sandviken, 1996 (Box 134, Folder 29)
  - Exit Art. Juan Sanchez, 1989 (Box 134, Folder 30)
  - Exit Art. Papo Colo, 1986 (Box 134, Folder 31)
  - Facades Imaginaires, undated (Box 134, Folder 32)
  - Farrell, Jeanette. Invisible Enemies, 1998 (Box 134, Folder 33)
  - Faulkner, Ray, Edwin Ziegfeld, and Howard Smagula. Art Today, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - The Fine Arts Program of the Redevelopment Authority, City of Philadelphia. City Art, undated (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Fordham University at Lincoln Center, Robert Moses Plaza. Environmental Sculpture, 1977 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Fordham University. Zigi Ben-Haim: "Journey With Me", 1997 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Freedman Gallery. Jackie Ferrara: Traversing Space, undated (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Freedman Gallery. Peter Campus: Selected Works 1973-1987 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Freedman Gallery. Surrounding Sculpture, 1998 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Freedman Gallery. Sites and Solutions: Recent Public Art, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Fried, Frederick, and Edmund V. Gillon, Jr. New York Civic Sculpture: A Pictorial Guide, 1976 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Galerie Daniel Tempton. Bernar Venet, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Galerie Michael Haas. Ilan Averbuch, 1990 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Galleria d'Arte Moderna Giorgio Morandi, Bologna. Pit Kroke, 1989 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Galleria Krista Mikkola. Richard Nonas, 1985 (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Gallery A. David Saunders, 1996 (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - Gallery One. Joyce Scott: I-con-no-body/I-con-o-graphy, 1991 (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - The Gershon Iskowitz Foundation. General Idea, 1989 (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - Gowan, Al. Nuts & Bolts, 1980 (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - Grace Borgenicht Gallery. David Saunders, 1983 (Box 135, Folder 18)
  - Graetz, Gidon. "Sculture in citta", 1998 (Box 135, Folder 19)
  - The Guild 8, undated (Box 135, Folder 20)
  - Guyon, Patrick. Zea Mays, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - Harcus Gallery. James Ford, undated (Box 135, Folder 22)
  - Hendry, Tom. Cultural Capital: The Care and Feeding of Toronto's Artistic Assets, 1985 (Box 135, Folder 23)
  - Hillwood Art Gallery. Grace Knowlton, undated (Box 135, Folder 24)
  - Hillwood Art Gallery. Insight on Site, undated (Box 135, Folder 25)
  - Hillwood Art Gallery. Public Art Program 1985-1988, undated (Box 135, Folder 26)
  - Hillwood Art Gallery. Seymour Lipton: Sculpture, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 27)
  - Hillwood Art Museum. Alan Sonfist 1969-1989, 1990 (Box 135, Folder 28)
  - Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden. A Garden for Art, undated (Box 135, Folder 29)
  - Hoffman, Jill. Mudfish 5, undated (Box 135, Folder 30)
  - Honolulu Academy of Arts. Dewain Valentine, 1985 (Box 135, Folder 31)
  - Hood College. Sydney K. Hamburger: Safe Spaces & Ritual Objects, 1993 (Box 135, Folder 32)
  - Humphrey Fine Art. Carol Kreeger Davidson, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 33)
  - Humphrey Fine Art. Carol Kreeger Davidson: Days of Danger, 1997 (Box 135, Folder 34)
  - International Sculptors Symposium. For Public Space, 1969-1970 (Box 135, Folder 35)
  - Iran America Society. Pierre Clerk, 1978 (Box 135, Folder 36)
  - Irish Museum of Modern Art. Pat Steir: 'A Painting Project', undated (Box 135, Folder 37)
  - The John and Mable Ringling Museum of Art. John Chamberlain: Reliefs 1960-1982, 1983 (Box 135, Folder 38)
  - John Kaldor Art Project. Sol Lewitt: Wall Pieces, 1998 (Box 135, Folder 39)
  - John Weber Gallery. Magdalena Jetelova, 1990 (Box 135, Folder 40)
  - Kleerebezem, Jouke. Andrea Blum: Domestic Arrangement/Public Affairs, 1997 (Box 135, Folder 41)
  - M. Knoedler & Co. Inc. David Smith (1906-1965), 1978 (Box 135, Folder 42)
  - Knoedler Contemporary Art. David Smith (1912-1965), 1974 (Box 135, Folder 43)
  - Knoedler & Company. Milton Avery: Edge of Abstraction, 1999 (Box 135, Folder 44)
  - Kolnischer Kunstverein. Peter Campus, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 45)
  - Kunsthalle Basel. Kristin Jones, Andrew Ginzel, 1989 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Kunsthalle Bern. Max Neuhaus: Two Sounds Works 1989 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Kunstraum Fuhrwerkswaage. Michel Gerard: Recycling Ashes, 1997 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Kunstverein Hannover. Kenneth Snelson, 1971 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - L'acceuil d'artistes en residence temporaire en France, 1992 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - La Jolla Museum of Contemporary Art. Jene Highstein, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - La Jolla Museum of Contemporary Art. Sitings, 1986 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - LaSalle Partners. The Private Eye in Public Art, 1997 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Laumeier Sculpture Park. Laumeier Sculpture Park: First Decade 1976-1986 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Laumeier Sculpture Park. Jackie Ferrara and Mary Miss, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Leicester, Andrew. Sketchbook, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Lennon, Weinberg, Inc. Raoul Hague, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Lincoln Center. Painting and Sculpture at Lincoln Center, undated (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Livability Digest, vol. 2 no. 1, 1982 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Long Island University. Judith Murray: Painting, Ursula von Rydingsvard: Sculpture, 1985 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - Long Island University. Public Art Project, undated (Box 136, Folder 16)
  - Lotan, Yael. Tumarkin: Etchings, Texts, Photos & Drawings, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 17)
  - Louis K. Meisel Gallery. Oded Halahmy, 1981 (Box 136, Folder 18)
  - Louis K. Meisel Gallery. Oded Halahmy: Bronze Sculptures 1981-1986, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 19)
  - Mackenzie Art Gallery. Pat Steir: Self-Portrait, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 20)
  - Madison Art Center. Owen Morrel: Works 1976-1984 (Box 136, Folder 21)
  - Marisa del Re Gallery. Arman's Orchestra, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 22)
  - Marisa del Re Gallery. IIIeme Biennale de Sculpture Montecarlo 1991 (Box 136, Folder 23)
  - Marlborough Chelsea. Beverly Pepper: The Magma Series, 2001 (Box 136, Folder 24)
  - Marlborough Gallery. Abakanowicz: Recent Exhibitions and Installations, undated (Box 136, Folder 25)
  - Marlborough Gallery. Charles Ginnever: Large Scale Sculpture, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 26)
  - Marlborough Gallery. Fernando Botero: Drawings on Canvas, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 27)
  - Marlborough Gallery. Magdalena Abakanowicz: Arboreal Architecture, 1992 (Box 136, Folder 28)
  - Marlborough Gallery. Marisol, 1995 (Box 136, Folder 29)
  - Maurine Littleton Gallery. Joyce Scott and Susan Plum, 1999 (Box 136, Folder 30)
  - Max Hutchinson Gallery. Clement Meadmore, undated (Box 136, Folder 31)
  - Max Hutchinson Gallery. James Buchanan, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 32)
  - Max Protetch Gallery. Scott Burton: Chaise Longings, 1996 (Box 136, Folder 33)
  - Max Protetch Gallery. Scott Burton: The Concrete Work, 1992 (Box 136, Folder 34)
  - Max Protetch Gallery. Siah Armajani: Elements, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 35)
  - MB Modern. Emily Mason, 1999 (Box 136, Folder 36)
  - McElheny, Josiah. The Metal Party, 2002 (Box 136, Folder 37)
  - Menegon, Lieutenant Colonel David J.. History of the Knickerbocker Greys, 2002 (Box 136, Folder 38)
  - Merriewold West Gallery. Outdoor Sculpture 1974 (Box 136, Folder 39)
  - Messner, Ann. Bearing Witness, undated (Box 136, Folder 40)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art. New York City Public Sculpture by 19th-Century American Artists, 1974 (Box 136, Folder 41)
  - Michael Rosenfeld Gallery. Burgoyne Diller, 1998 (Box 136, Folder 42)
  - Midtown Payson Galleries. Joyce Kozloff, 1995 (Box 136, Folder 43)
  - Milgo Art Systems. Kosso Eloul, undated (Box 136, Folder 44)
  - Minnesota Highway Project, undated (Box 136, Folder 45)
  - Moffett, Donald. Blue [NY], 1997 (Box 136, Folder 46)
  - Municipal Art Society. Adopt-A-Monument, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 47)
  - Murdock, Robert M. The Sculpture of Bill Freeland, 1989 (Box 136, Folder 48)
  - Musee Departemental des Vosges. Michel Gerard, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 49)
  - Museum of Art, The Pennsylvania State University. Rodney Alan Greenblat's Reality and Imagination; Two Taste Treats in One, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 50)
  - The Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles. Saber es poder/interventions, 1994 (Box 136, Folder 51)
  - The Museum of Modern Art, New York. Painting and Sculpture in the Museum of Modern Art, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Museum of Modern Art, Oxford. David Mach: Towards a Landscape, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Nassau County Museum of Fine Art. Allen Bertoldi 1941-1981: Retrospective, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Nassau County Museum of Fine Art. Edward Mayer: Sculpture, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Nassau County Museum of Fine Arts. Mary Miss: Perimeters/Pavilions/Decoys, 1978 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Nassau County Museum of Fine Arts. Passings: Robert Stackhouse, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Nassau County Museum of Fine Art. Richard Nonas, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. Five Artists at NOAA, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - New Jersey State Museum. A Force of Repetition, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Nohra Haime Gallery. Keith Milow: Recent Work, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Nohra Haime Gallery. Lika Mutal: Recent Sculpture, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Nohra Haime Gallery. Lika Mutal: Stone Sculpture, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Nohra Haime Gallery. Menashe Kadishman: Small Sculpture, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Nonas, Richard. Agricultural Doubt, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Nordman, Maria. De Musica, undated (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - NYSCA Visual Artists Program: Responses from the Organizational Profile Questionnaire, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - The Oakland Museum. Public Sculpture/Urban Environment, 1974 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Orte: Kunst fur offentliche Raume, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - Oscarsson Hood Gallery. Marsha Pels, 1984-1985 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - The Pace Gallery. Ape & Cat, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 20)
  - The Pace Gallery. Barry Flanagan, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 21)
  - The Parks Council and Central Park Conservancy. Public Space for Public Life, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 22)
  - Patrick Dougherty, undated (Box 137, Folder 23)
  - Paula Cooper Gallery. Tony Smith: Stinger, 1999 (Box 137, Folder 24)
  - Percent for Art: A Review, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 25)
  - Philippe Staib Gallery. Owen Morrel, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 26)
  - Philippe Staib Gallery. Zero Higashida, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 27)
  - Pittsburgh Center for the Arts. Michael Hardesty, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 28)
  - Pittsburgh Center for the Arts. Robert Arneson: Points of View, 1986 (Box 137, Folder 29)
  - Platz-Haus Salgau. Kurt Laurenz Metzler, 1996 (Box 137, Folder 30)
  - Plenn, Virginia & Jaime. A Guide to Modern Mexican Murals, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 31)
  - The Port Authority of NY & NJ. The Arts as an Industry, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 32)
  - Pratt Institute Department of Exhibitions. Bridges, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 33)
  - Public Art Development Trust, undated (Box 137, Folder 34)
  - Public Art Fund. Allison Smith: The Muster, 2005 (Box 137, Folder 35)
  - Public Art Fund. Contemporary Art at the Embassy Suites Hotel in New York City, 2000 (Box 137, Folder 36)
  - Public Art Fund. Everyday Eden, 2007 (Box 137, Folder 37)
  - Public Art Fund. Field Guide to the Wildlife of Madison Square Park, 2002 (Box 137, Folder 38)
  - Public Art Fund. Francis Alys: The Modern Procession, 2004 (Box 137, Folder 39)
  - Public Art Fund. Governors Island, 2004 (Box 137, Folder 40)
  - Public Art Fund. The Invisible City, undated (Box 137, Folder 41)
  - Public Art Fund. Issues, 1989-1992 (Box 137, Folder 42)
  - Public Art Fund. Julian Opie, 2004 (Box 137, Folder 43)
  - Public Art Fund. Now Entering Brooklyn, 2003 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Public Art Fund Publications: 01, 02, 03, 04, 05, 06, 2000-2003 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Public Art Fund. Semiprecious, 2004 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Public Art Fund. Roxy Paine/Bluff, undated (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Public Art Fund. Ten Years of Public Art 1972-1982 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Public Art Fund. Tony Oursler: The Influence Machine, undated (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Public Art Fund. Trapdoor, 2008 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Public Art Fund. Urban Paradise: Gardens in the City, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Public Art Fund. The World is Round, 2006 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Public Art Works: 1989 Annual Catalog (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Public Arts Council of the Municipal Art Society. Pierre Clerk at Waterside, 1977 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Produzentengalerie Hamburg. Bogomir Ecker, 1987 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - P.S.1. Contemporary Art Center. Clockwork 2000, 1999 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Queens College, City University of New York. The Ways of Wood, 1984-1985 (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - The Queens Museum. Sculpture of the Eighties, 1987 (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Randolph Street Gallery. Outdoor Installations 1979-1980 (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Reed, Henry Hope, Robert M. McGee, and Esther Mipaas. Bridges of Central Park, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - Rist, Pipilotti. I'm not the girl who misses much, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - Robert Elkon Gallery. William Tucker: Sculpture and Drawings, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 19)
  - Robert Miller Gallery. Juan Hamilton, 1987 (Box 138, Folder 20)
  - Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, Inc., and the Village Voice. The 1984 Show (Box 138, Folder 21)
  - Royal Festival Hall. Silvio Wolf: The Elsewhere [A/V: CD-Rom catalogue], 1999 (Box 138, Folder 22)
  - Ruth Siegel Gallery. Creighton Michael: Constructions 1990 (Box 138, Folder 23)
  - Sacramento Metropolitan Arts Commission. Sculpture Sacramento, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 24)
  - Salvatore Ala Gallery. Antony Gormley, 1984 (Box 138, Folder 25)
  - Salvatore Ala Gallery. David Finn: Masked Figures, 1986 (Box 138, Folder 26)
  - San Francisco Department of City Planning. The Downtown Plan, 1983 (Box 138, Folder 27)
  - San Francisco Museum of Art. Beverly Pepper: Sculpture 1971-1975 (Box 138, Folder 28)
  - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art. The Clos Pegase Design Competition, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 29)
  - San Jose Museum of Art. Fletcher Benton, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 30)
  - Sculpture 3: New York Artists on Tour, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 31)
  - Sculpture Off the Pedestal, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 32)
  - Sculpture Outside in Cleveland, 1981 (Box 138, Folder 33)
  - Sculpture Outdoors. Out of the Woods, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 34)
  - SculptureCenter. Alan Finkel: SculptureCenter Prize 2001 (Box 138, Folder 35)
  - Seattle Arts Commission. Artwork Network, 1984 (Box 138, Folder 36)
  - Shingu, Susumu. Windcircus, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 37)
  - Sidney Janis Gallery. R.M. Fischer: New Sculpture, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 38)
  - Socrates Sculpture Park. Artists Choose Artists, 1988 (Box 138, Folder 39)
  - Socrates Sculpture Park. Sculptors Working, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 40)
  - Socrates Sculpture Park. Socrates Sculpture Park Inaugural Exhibition, 1986 (Box 138, Folder 41)
  - Soffer, Sasson. Sasson Soffer: In the City of New York, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 42)
  - Soffer, Sasson. Sasson Soffer: Metal Sculptures, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 43)
  - Spitzer, Serge. Hannover Relevator, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Stadtische Kunsthalle Dusseldorf. Bogomir Ecker, 1989 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Stadtische Kunsthalle Mannheim. Michel Gerard: Skulpturen 1976-1988 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Stadtisches Kunstmuseum Bonn. Bogomir Ecker, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Stark Gallery. Jill Baroff, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 5)